[
  {
    "id": 1764680058795,
    "title": "Math Quiz",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "2+2?",
        "option1": "3",
        "option2": "4",
        "option3": "5",
        "option4": "6",
        "ans": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "5*3?",
        "option1": "15",
        "option2": "10",
        "option3": "20",
        "option4": "25",
        "ans": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "10/2?",
        "option1": "2",
        "option2": "5",
        "option3": "8",
        "option4": "10",
        "ans": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "7-3?",
        "option1": "3",
        "option2": "4",
        "option3": "5",
        "option4": "6",
        "ans": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "12+8?",
        "option1": "18",
        "option2": "20",
        "option3": "22",
        "option4": "24",
        "ans": 2
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1764680058800,
    "title": "Internet & Devices Quiz",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
        "option1": "Modem",
        "option2": "Router",
        "option3": "LAN Cable",
        "option4": "Pen Drive",
        "ans": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Which programming language is primarily used for web development?",
        "option1": "Python",
        "option2": "HTML",
        "option3": "C++",
        "option4": "Java",
        "ans": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "Which protocol is used to send emails?",
        "option1": "HTTP",
        "option2": "FTP",
        "option3": "SMTP",
        "option4": "DNS",
        "ans": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is a type of computer network?",
        "option1": "WAN",
        "option2": "LAN",
        "option3": "MAN",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "ans": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "Which language is used for Android app development?",
        "option1": "Java",
        "option2": "Python",
        "option3": "C#",
        "option4": "Ruby",
        "ans": 1
      }
    ]
  }
]
